字幕组
ZiMuZu.tv
《闪电侠》和《超女》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash" and "Supergirl"...
他怎么了
What just happened to him?
沃利取代了我在神速力中的位置
Wally has taken my place in the Speed Force.
没事  我们回家了
It's okay, we're going home.
沃利所目睹的  会困扰他好一阵
What Wally saw, it's gonna haunt him for a while.
我求婚是因为我觉得那样可以救你
I proposed because I thought it would save you.
-什么意思  -我们需要分开一阵子
- What does that mean? - I think we need some space.
我应该告诉你实话  我叫蒙·艾尔
I owe you the truth. My name is Mon-El.
我是达克萨姆星以前的王子
I'm the former Prince of Daxam.
我不该被骗的
I deserve better than being lied to.
我一直在找你
I've been looking for you.
拜拜
Toodles!
*我在雨中歌唱*
*I'm singin' in the rain*
我告诉过你了
I told you.
18年前
歌声中的世界更美好
Everything's better in song.
你说话时吐露的仅仅是词语
When you speak, it's just words.
而你歌唱时  你敞开了自己的灵魂
But when you sing, you open up your soul
让真正的自己闪闪发光
and let who you really are shine through.
谢谢  妈妈
Thanks, Mom.
我爱你  乖儿子
I love you, my beautiful boy.
我也爱你
I love you too.
*乌云变朗日*
*I'm happy again*
*我嘲笑乌云*
*I'm laughing at clouds*
*高高在上  暗黑压抑*
*So dark up above*
这...
This...
又听啊
Again?
怎么  你打算余生
What, are you gonna spend the rest of your life
都坐在沙发上吗  起来
sitting around on the couch? Come on.
你已经这样好几天了  起来做点事
You've been doing this for days. Let's do something.
-我们出去  -不  抱歉
- Let's go out. - No, man, I'm sorry.
我不想出去
I--I don't feel like going out.
这些天你为什么总听这些音乐剧
What is it with you and musicals these days anyhow?
歌声中的世界更美好
Everything's better in song.
兄弟  我知道
Listen, dude, I know
自从爱瑞丝取消订婚后
you've been going through a tough time
你过得不好
since Iris broke off the engagement,
-或者我猜...  -什么
- or, I guess... - What?
准确说  自从你取消订婚后
Technically, since you broke off the engagement.
无论谁取消订婚
Whoever broke off the engagement,
都不重要  我只是...
it doesn't matter, I just--
我不知道  我只是想帮你
I don't know, man. I want to help.
你帮不上什么
Nothing you can really do.
是吗  我只要让
Really? I guess I'm just gonna
吉恩·凯利先生来接手就好
have to let Mr. Gene Kelly take over
《雨中曲》的男主角
天啊  因为我对这个可真是没法子
'cause, Lord knows, I can't do anything about that.
-HR打来的  -好吧
- It's H.R. - Yeah.
BA
B.A.,
有人要穿过来了
someone's coming through.
可能是吉普赛
Could be Gypsy.
可能吧  也可能是...
Could be, or it could be--
超女
Supergirl?
卡拉
Kara...
她怎么了
What happened to her?
我们不知道
We don't know,
但这么做的人已经到这个世界来了
but whoever did it has come to this world.
闪电侠
第三季
第十七集
她的生命体征很弱
Her vitals are low.
她这样多久了
How long has she been like this?
几个小时
A few hours.
我们得找到这样对卡拉的人
Okay, we need to find whoever did this to Kara
然后揍到他逆转
and punch him repeatedly until he reverses
卡拉身上的咒语  而且我得第一个揍他
whatever spell he put on her, and I get to punch him first.
你到底是谁
Who are you exactly?
我是蒙·艾尔
My name is Mon-El.
我是卡拉的...
I'm--I'm Kara's...
朋友
friend.
我们不只是朋友
We're more-- more than friend.
我们接吻过好几次了
We've been kissing a lot.
她从没说过她有男朋友
Oh, she never mentioned she had a boyfriend.
这是最近的事
It's a recent thing, so...
我以为你们俩分手了
I thought you two broke up.
这么告诉你吧  我很清楚
I tell you what, I know enough not to mention
所以不去提巴里他们分手的事
the breakup between Barry and--uh--
-HR  -抱歉
- H.R. - Sorry.
无论我和卡拉之间发生什么事
Look, hey, whatever's going on between me and Kara,
我不能让她这个样子
I cannot leave her like this, okay?
-我要把她救回来  -我们会的  我保证
- I need to get her back. - We will, I promise.
她到底出了什么事
So what happened to her?
外星人囚犯从我们这逃脱了
An alien prisoner escaped our custody.
他对她做了什么  让她陷入了昏迷
He did something to her, put her in some kind of a coma.
然后就消失了
And then he disappeared.
我们追踪到他来了这  所以就跟来了
We tracked him here and followed.
但他为什么来到这个地球
Okay, but why would he come to this Earth?
我们认为
Well, we believe...
是来找你的
for you.
-找我  为什么  -不清楚
- Me? Why? - We don't know.
但他消失的最后一句话
But his last words before he disappeared
说是要找现今世上速度最快的人
were about finding the fastest man alive.
好吧  显然
Okay, well, clearly,
有穿越者来了这里
we're talking about a breacher here.
只有一件事我能做
And if there's one thing I can do,
就是找到穿越者
it's find breachers.
对于这家伙  你们还知道些什么
So what else can you tell us about this guy?
知道得不多
Not much.
他就像是凭空出现的
It's like he just materialized out of thin air.
就像这个小丑一样吗
You mean like this clown just did?
我要走了
I'm gonna go.
华莱士
Wallace...
我明白你所经历过的事
I understand what you've been through.
困在神速力里时所看到的事物  我明白
Stuck in the Speed Force, things you saw... I get it.
我也知道有时  古话说得没错
I also know that sometimes, the old adage is true.
当你从马背上摔下时
When you get bucked from the horse,
你能做的只有
best thing you can do...
爬上去再接再厉  华莱士
get right back on the damn thing and ride, Wallace.
继续驰骋吧
Ride!
你好啊  巴里·艾伦
Hello, Barry Allen.
-你怎么知道...  -知道你的名字吗
- How do you-- - Know your name?
我知道很多事
I know a lot of things.
也能做很多事
And I can do a lot of things too.
沃利·韦斯特也来了
Wally West made it here too.
真是兴奋啊
This is exciting.
你能一起来玩真是太好了  闪电小子
It's good of you to join the party, Kid Flash.
很高兴你能来
I'm happy to have you.
你要把超女怎么样
What do you want with Supergirl?
和对你们俩一样
Same thing that I want with both of you.
给你们所有人上一课
To teach you all a lesson.
你就这点能耐吗  闪电小子
Is that all you got, Kid Flash?
你好像有点害怕啊
I mean, you look a little scared.
而你太慢了
And you're too slow.
晚安了  闪电侠
Nighty-night, Flash.
*月亮*
*Moon...*
搞什么
What the hell?
*河*
*River*
*水波过英里*
*Wider than a mile*
*总有一天*
*I'm crossing...*
卡拉
Kara?
*我会优雅地遇见你*
*You in style someday*
*造梦之河*
*Oh, dream maker*
*心碎之河*
*You heart breaker*
*无论流向何处*
*Wherever you're going*
*我都会紧追不舍*
*I'm going your way*
*你我结伴流浪*
*Two drifters*
*踏遍山河*
*Off to see the world*
*大千世界  尽情探索*
*There's such a lot of world to see*
*望着同一道*
*We're after*
*彩虹尽头*
*The same...rainbow's end*
*在河湾等候*
*Waiting 'round the bend*
*我亲爱的好友*
*My huckleberry friend*
*月亮河*
*Moon river*
*还有我*
*And me...*
唱得真动听
What a singer, huh?
-是啊  -你认识她
- Yeah. - You know her?
认识
Yeah, I do.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen...
巴里
Barry?
巴里  是你  谢谢拉奥
Barry! It's you, thank Rao!
等等  真的是你吧
Oh, wait, it's really you, right?
-是我  没错  -那就好
- Yeah, this is me, yeah. - Good.
我们到底在哪  怎么回事
What is-- where the hell are we? What's going on?
我还指望你能告诉我呢
I was hoping you could tell me
或者解释下为什么我会扮成奥黛丽·赫本
or maybe explain to me why I just pulled an Audrey Hepburn
在夜店里唱歌
and sang in a nightclub.
-也许我们在做梦  -做相同的梦
- Maybe we're dreaming? - The same dream?
是有点  你在来这里之前
Yeah, that's... what's the last thing
所记得的最后一件事是什么
you remember before you got here?
我在超查部
I was at the D.E.O.
他们带来了一个外星罪犯
They had just brought in an alien prisoner.
他逃脱了  然后...
He got loose, and--
当时挺奇怪的  他有那么个红色的...
It was really weird. He had this, um, red--
-口袋手帕  -没错
- Pocket handkerchief? - Yes!
我在我的地球上看到你昏迷着
I saw you on my Earth. You were in a coma.
你的男朋友把你带来的
Your boyfriend brought you to us.
他不是我男朋友
He is not my boyfriend.
他就是个男孩
He--he's just a boy.
才不是我朋友
Who is not my friend.
-他跟我什么都不是  -好吧
- He's my nothing. - Okay.
好吧  不管他是谁
All right, uh, well, whoever he is
他说那个人给你施了咒
said that this guy whammied you,
然后逃到了我的地球
and then he escaped to my Earth,
他出现在了尖端科研实验室
he showed up at S.T.A.R. Labs,
我去追他  想让他唤醒你
I went after him to try to get him to wake you up--
-然后你也被下咒了  -是啊
- And then you got whammied. - Yeah.
-那我们这是在哪  -我不知道
- So where are we? - I don't know.
这里可能是平行宇宙  或者...
I mean, it could be a parallel dimension, or...
可能是某种精心设计的幻觉
maybe just some elaborate illusion.
咱们得找个逃脱的办法
We just need to figure a way out.
或许我可以试试敲鞋跟三次
I guess I could click my heels together three times.
《绿野仙踪》中桃乐丝敲鞋跟三次就能去想去的地方
-行啊  -我是开玩笑的
- Yeah-- - I was kidding.
好吧  那么...
Okay, all right, well...
来吧  咱们去...
Come on. Let's...
话说你歌唱得真不错
You're a really good singer, by the way.
谢了  我姐姐说
Hey, thanks. My sister says
卡拉OK里的卡拉就是我
I put the "Kara" in "Karaoke."
你们在这里啊
There you are!
梅林
Merlyn...
-谁  -谁
- Who? - Who?
马尔科姆·梅林
Malcolm Merlyn.
刺客联盟的前头领
Former head of the League of Assassins.
什么的什么
The what of the what?
你在胡扯些什么  小鬼
What the hell you talking about, kid?
我的名字是卡特·莫兰  这家俱乐部的主人
My name's Cutter Moran, I own this club,
你俩都是为我工作的
and both of you work for me.
-我们什么  -我付钱请你俩唱歌
- We what now? - I pay you to sing,
不是来给我提问的
not pepper me with questions.
而且我希望你们的曲库里有
And I hope you got something better in your songbook
比刚才在那里唱得要好的歌  金发妞
than what you were belting out up there, blondie.
不许叫我金发妞
Hey! Don't call me blondie.
听着  我不知道你是谁...
Hey, look, I don't know who you are--
显然您是位用小刀的好手
obviously you're someone who's quick with a knife.
请原谅我这位朋友
You have to excuse my friend.
他说话不加思考的
He doesn't think before he talks.
我有个表兄弟也这样
Yeah, I had a cousin like that.
我只好割了他的喉
I had to slit his throat too.
格雷迪  让他们俩准备好
Grady! Get these two set up.
还有唱点我没听过的
And nothing I've heard before.
我想要原创
I want something original.
巴里  我在这里没有能力
Barry, I don't have my powers.
我也没有
Me neither.
温
Winn!
温  你也来了吗
Winn, you're here too?
温是谁  我叫格雷迪
Ah! Who's Winn? The name is Grady.
我是这里弹钢琴的
I tickle the keys around here.
你知道他怎么得到"切割者"这个别名的吧
Say, you realize how he got the nickname "Cutter,"
-是吧  -不知道
- don't you? - No.
因为他喜欢拿刀割人
Because he likes to cut people.
要我说  他就是嘴炮
You ask me, I think he's all talk.
西斯科  不是西斯科  你好
Cisco... Not Cisco. Hello.
我希望不会有那么一天
I pray that, one day, you do not find out
你发现你大错特错了  帕布洛
how very, very wrong you are, Pablo.
-回去干你的活  -好吧
- Now go do your job. - All right.
格雷迪还不知道  但总有一天
You see, Grady doesn't know this, but one day,
我会声名大噪
I'm gonna be somebody.
我会声名大噪  而且
I'm gonna be somebody, and it's gonna happen
就在这个舞台上
right there on that stage.
等着瞧  我只是需要一个机会
You'll see. I just need my one shot.
越来越稀奇了
It's just curiouser and curiouser.
对  就好像是《绿野仙踪》
Yeah, yeah, it's like "The Wizard of Oz."
-是啊  -你一会儿在那里
- Yeah. - "And you were there,
-一会儿在这里  -但却不是真的他们
- and you were there...." - Except, it's not really them.
他们都是音乐剧里的
They're all playing characters in a...
角色
musical.
巴里  我们在哪
Barry, where are we?
我不知道
I don't know.
大家都说
Well, you knew what they say...
演出必须继续
the show must go on!
超女  我喜欢你演绎的《月亮河》
Supergirl, I loved your rendition of "Moon River,"
实在是太美了
such a beautiful song.
有些地方你音唱低了些
You were a little flat in places,
不过你这么可爱  那也过得去吧
but I'm willing to let it slide just because you're so cute.
等等  你对我们做了什么
Hold on. What did you do to us?
没什么
Oh, nothing much.
只是在你们心中放了一点歌声
Just put a little song in your heart.
放了一点
Put a little--
你为什么带我们到这里来
Why did you bring us here?
我没有带你们去哪
I didn't bring you anywhere.
我们在你们的脑海里
We're inside your heads.
你们创造了这个世界
You created this world.
我们太幸运了  本来可能会是在战争电影里
And we got lucky because it could have been a war movie
或者太空探险片里
or a--a space opera,
但幸好你们喜欢音乐剧
but thanks to your love of musicals,
你和养父母一起看了无数遍
with the countless times you watched, um, "Wizard of Oz"
-《绿野仙踪》  -你怎么知道
- with your adoptive parents... - How did you know that?
还有你  那些个下雨的夜晚
And, you, all those rainy nights
和妈妈一起看弗雷德·阿斯泰尔和弗兰克·辛纳屈
watching Fred Astaire and Frank Sinatra with Mom.
不然我们还能去哪呢
Well, where else would we be?
好吧  够了
All right, all right.
想打我  打不到吧
Swing and a miss.
我还没告诉你
I didn't tell you.
我其实不在这里
I'm not really here.
我在外面的真实世界里
See, I'm out there in the real world.
中城是我唾手可得的了
Central City's mine for the taking.
我们会阻止你的
Ah. We're gonna stop you.
对
Yeah!
欢迎你们来尝试
You're welcome to try that.
前提是你们能出去的话
If you can get out of here.
我们怎么出去
How do we get out of here?
你们在音乐剧电影里
You're in a movie musical.
所以你们要做的就是  跟着
So all you have to do is just follow the--
黄砖路
The Yellow Brick Road?
桃乐丝寻找大魔术师要经过的路
不是  跟着剧本啊
No, the--the script.
-哦对  -剧本
- Oh, yeah. - Script...
到了剧情的结局
Reach the end of the plot,
嘛哩嘛哩哄  你们就能回家了
and, presto chango, you get to go home.
不过有个小细节我得说明白
One little detail, though, I should mention...
这里的你死了  真实世界的你也死了
if you die in here, you die out there.
真好
Lovely.
我真是受够魔法怪人了
I've reached my limit with magical creeps.
同时  我希望你们都准备好了
In the meantime, I hope you're both ready
开嗓一展歌喉
to get the rust off those pipes of yours.
-我们才不唱给你听  -才不
- We're not singing for you! - No.
不会再唱了
Uh, any--anymore, I mean.
别这样  也许来点
Come on, now, maybe just one little
-有趣的开场节奏就能  -别脱外套
- fun opening number just to... - Leave your jacket on.
-开始表演了  -去哪儿了
- kick things off! - Where did it go?
*想起你的同胞时*
*Think of your fellow man*
-住口  -不可能的
- Stop that. - It's not happening.
*援助之手别吝惜*
*Lend him a helping hand*
-行不通的  -我们才不唱
- It's not gonna work. - We're not singing!
*放一份爱在心里*
*Put a little love in your heart*
*眼看就要来不及*
*You see it's getting late*
*请不要忸忸怩怩*
*Oh, please don't hesitate*
*放一份爱在心里*
*Put a little love in your heart*
*世界*
*And the world *-
-*世界*  -*会更加美丽*
- *The world... * - *Will be a better place*
-*世界*  -*世界*
- *And the world * - *The world*
*会更加美丽*
*Will be a better place*
-*你*  -*我都将受益*
- *For you * - *And me*
*请君*
*You just wait*
*静候佳音*
*And see, yeah*
*若要世界知悉*
*If you want the world to know*
*仇恨无法林立*
*We won't let hatred grow*
*放一份爱在心里*
*Put a little love in your heart*
*世界*
*And the world*
*会更加美丽*
*Will be a better place*
*世界*
*And the world*
*会更加美丽*
*Will be a better place*
-*你和我*  -*你和我*
- *For you * - *For you*
-*都将受益*  -*都将受益*
- *And me * - *And me*
*请君静候佳音*
*You just wait and see*
*最好认真环顾四周*
*You better take a good look around*
*若能看到低微之地*
*Oh, if you're looking down*
*放一份爱在心里*
*Put a little love in your heart*
*世界*
*And the world*
*会更加美丽*
*Will be a better place*
-*世界各处*  -*世界各处*
- *All the world * - *All the world*
*会更加美丽*
*Will be a better place*
-*你和我*  -*你和我*
- *For you * - *For you*
-*都将受益*  -*都将受益*
- *And me * - *And me*
*请君静候佳音*
*You just wait and see*
*放一份爱在心里*
*Put a little love in your heart*
*放一份爱  放一份爱*
*Put a little love, put a little love*
*放一份爱在心里*
*Put a little love in your heart*
*放一份爱*
*Put a little love*
*放一份爱在心里*
*Put a little love in your heart*
*来吧*
*Come on and...*
*放一份爱在心里*
*Put a little love in your heart...*
他人呢
Where'd he go?
不知道
I don't know.
我们去找他
Come on, let's find him.
-他消失了  -没错
- He's gone. - Yup.
我们现在怎么办
So what do we do now?
不知道  也许我们就
I don't know, I mean, I guess we just...
按他说的做吧
We do what he says, right?
我们得弄清楚音乐剧的情节
We have to figure out what the plot of the musical is,
-然后跟着故事走  -好吧  那么...
- and we follow the story. - Okay, uh, so...
我们目前有何线索
What do we know so far?
我们是歌手
We're singers.
而且很明显  我们为恶棍工作
And apparently we work for a gangster.
没错  还想让我们为他表演
Yes, who wants us to perform for him.
说实话  这剧情挺直白的
I mean, honestly, it's pretty straightforward.
-是吧  -没错
- Right? - Yeah.
你们好
Hello.
好啊  我想念刀枪不入的能力
Hi! I miss being bulletproof.
你们跟我们走
You're coming with us.
谁说的
Says who?
我说的
Says me.
巴里  你没事吧
Barry, are you okay?
别吼了
Oh, please stop yelling.
我没吼
I'm not yelling.
等等  我们在哪儿
Wait, where are we?
我不知道
I don't know.
好吧  我确定尖端科研实验室的人
All right, well, I'm sure everybody at S.T.A.R. Labs
都在想办法救我们出去
is working on getting us out of this.
是啊  幸好他们带我去了你的地球
Yeah, I'm glad they brought me to your Earth.
蒙·艾尔好像很在意你
Mon-El seems like he really cares about you.
蒙·艾尔只在意他自己
Mon-El only cares about himself.
他向我隐瞒了身份
He lied to me about who he really is
长达九个月
for nine months.
我无法释怀
I can't shake it.
我还以为我们之间很特别呢
I thought it was gonna be something special
就像你和爱瑞丝一样
like what you have with Iris.
我们的感情
That is...
出了问题
off track.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我向她求了婚
I asked her to marry me.
是吗  那很棒啊
You did? That's great.
她答应了吗
Did she not say yes?
她本来答应了  但我出于其他原因
Oh, she said yes, but I guess I did it
才向她求婚  我确实爱她
for the wrong reason, and, I mean, I love her,
但我也想改变未来
but I was trying to change the future.
我太想救她  反而疏远了她
Then I pushed her away so I could focus on saving her,
现在是一团糟
and it's just a mess now.
我飞奔时  一切都很简单
Everything's so simple when I'm running.
我飞翔时也是
Or flying.
闭嘴
Shut up!
你俩都闭嘴
Both of you.
斯泰因
Stein?
斯泰因是谁
Who--who's Stein?
好吧
Right.
就是他们吗
This them?
没错
Yeah.
你们知道我是谁吗
Do you know who I am?
我猜不是乔·韦斯特
Not Joe West, I'm guessing.
迪格西  迪格西·福斯
Digsy. Digsy Foss.
这座城市归我管
I run this town.
所以你是市长吗
So you're the mayor?
虽然市长赢了选票
The mayor may have gotten the vote...
但大权还是在我手里
but I got the power.
我遇到了麻烦...
I got a situation...
你们两个要帮我
that you two are gonna help me with.
我们很乐意帮忙
We would love to help you with it.
真的很乐意
Really love to.
我的女儿  米莉
My daughter, Millie...
她失踪了
She's missing.
她最后一次被看见时
Last she was seen,
她正前往卡特·莫兰的地盘
she was heading into Cutter Moran's place.
你们在那儿见过她了吗
Have you seen her in there?
-你是说她叫米莉吗  -是的  为什么这么问
- Millie, did you say? - Yeah. Why?
我们没见过她  我没见过她
We haven't seen her. I haven't seen her
-我也没见过她  -我们...
- I haven't seen her. - Yeah, we...
她是我生命中唯一的美好
She's the only thing that is good and decent about my life.
如果她有个三长两短
If anything happened to her,
我就要血洗这座城市
this town will run red with blood.
从你们开始下手
Starting with yours.
我们可能不想变成那样  对吗
We wouldn't want that, now, right?
我们要怎么帮你
So, um, how can we help you?
你们俩为卡特唱歌
You two sing for Cutter.
-没错是我们  -是的  是我们
- We sure do. - Yes, we do.
你们可以四处打听看看能不能找到她的下落
You could poke around and see if you can find her.
那么  你们会帮我吗
So are you gonna do this for me?
我们要怎么办
What do we do?
跟着剧本走
Follow the script.
我们会找到她的  先生
We're gonna find her... Sir.
很好
Good.
好了  就是这里
Okay. This is the place.
4B号公寓
Apartment 4B.
这里能找到爱瑞丝吗
This is where we can find Iris?
-是米莉  -米莉  对
- Millie. - Millie, right.
没错  她就在里面
Yeah, she's in there, all right.
现在  你们给我听好了
Now, you two listen to me.
不要告诉任何人是我带你们来这里的
Don't you go telling anyone I showed you this.
当然  我们保证不告诉别人
Oh, yeah, we promise.
给你们点忠告
Word to the wise.
你们这样一探究竟
You go digging around in this dirt...
最后发现的东西可不讨喜
you might not like what you find.
好的
Okay.
好吧  记住  她可能长得像爱瑞丝
Okay, so remember, she might look like Iris,
但她不是爱瑞丝
but she is not Iris.
我知道  这很奇怪
I know. This is gonna be weird.
可不是吗
Yeah, tell me about it.
还好我们没有见到和蒙·艾尔长得一样的人
I'm glad we haven't seen someone that looks like Mon-El.
我可能会直接揍他一拳寻开心
I'd probably just punch him in the face for the fun of it.
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
是她  听起来她遇到麻烦了
That's her. Sounds like she's in trouble.
靠后站  我要把门踢开
Here, stand back, I'm gonna kick the door in.
你靠后站  我来把门踢开
You stand back, I'll kick the door in.
我不是嫌你是个女的
Well, I didn't mean, like, a gender thing.
-我只是想把门踢开  -巴里
- I just wanted to kick it in-- - Barry!
好吧  一起  好吗
All right, together. All right?
-一  二  -三
- One, two... - Three!
这是怎么回事
What the hell is going on?
好吧  被你们发现了
All right, you caught us.
我们恋爱了
We're in love.
好恶心
Ugh, gross.
各位  我们有个问题
Guys, we have a problem.
又一个问题
Well, another problem.
巴里细胞中的神速力等级
The Speed Force levels in Barry's cells
被严重耗尽了
have been severely depleted,
卡拉体内的太阳辐射也是一样
as has the amount of solar radiation in Kara's body.
这是什么意思
What exactly does that mean?
他们被抽干了
They're being drained.
对他们下手的人
The guy who did this to them...
我想是在偷取他们的超能力
I think he's stealing their powers.
中心城市银行
启动
Power up.
中心城市银行
我们得把他抓来
We gotta bring him in.
不是我们  是我
No, not we-- me.
是我让巴里被下了咒
I'm the reason Barry got whammied.
无论输赢  我们都是一个团队
We win and we lose as a team.
我和你一起去
I'm coming with you.
我也去
I'm coming too.
你看  约翰
Look, John, uh,
我尊重你现在的特工身份
I respect this whole special agent situation
但现在咱们遇到的问题
you got going on, but this problem right here
需要一位有着...
needs someone with...
绿皮肤和酷炫披风的人
Green skin and sick-ass cape.
叫我火星猎人
Call me the Martian Manhunter.
我想你们会发现约翰
I think you'll find that John's a lot more
不只有张帅脸
than just a pretty face.
大伙
Guys!
你好
Hello.
巴里和卡拉的生命特征开始混乱了
Also, Barry and Kara's vitals are all over the place.
我们走
Let's go.
好吧
All right.
你们好  朋友们
Hello, friends!
中心
城市
银行
闪电小子
Kid Flash.
真高兴你也来参加派对
Oh, I'm so glad you could join the party.
我很崇拜你的  但我要说
I'm such a huge fan of your work, but I have to say,
最近你做得不怎么样了啊
recently, your work's been a bit off.
你明白我的意思吧
You know what I'm talking about?
我觉得可能是你有点害怕
I think maybe it's just that you're a little scared
因为神速力里发生的事
from what happened in the Speed Force.
是吗
Is that it?
不是
No,
我什么都不怕
and I'm not afraid of anything.
那就证明吧
Prove it.
西斯科  他们正去往第四街和阿斯本街交口
Uh, Cisco, they're headed towards 4th and Aspen.
收到
Got it.
这边走
This way.
好了  约翰
All right, Jonn,
你觉得来点强强组合如何
how do you feel about a little one-two combo?
我来打开缺口  你准备好用尽全力
I'm gonna open a breach, you be ready to hit something
攻击另一面
really hard on the B-side.
用力  我可以做到
Hitting hard, I can do.
沃利  准备好在地面上
Wally, get ready to do the same thing
进行同样的攻击
on the ground level.
收到
Copy.
就是现在
Now!
晚安啦
Nighty-night.
你们是谁
Hey, who are you?
报上你们的名字
Your names, now.
我是卡拉  他是巴里
I'm Kara. This is Barry.
我们是你爸爸夜店里的歌手
We're singers at your dad's nightclub.
米莉  你爸爸以为你被绑架了
Millie, your dad thinks you've been kidnapped.
很明显他搞错了
Well, clearly he's mistaken.
他真的希望你能回家
He really wants you to come home.
听着  我再也不会回去
Listen, I am never going back there.
为什么
Why not?
"再没有像家一样的地方了"
"There's no place like home."
托米·莫兰
Tommy Moran...
就是我的家
is my home.
而且  如果老头子们知道了这事
And besides, if our geezers ever caught wind of this,
他们会打起来的
they'd go to war.
那遭殃就不仅仅是我们了
It'd be the end of more than just us, huh?
托米说得没错
Yeah, Tommy's right.
我们的爸爸讨厌对方
Our fathers hate each other.
我们是不能相爱的
Our love is forbidden.
这简直就是《西区故事》
This is just like "West Side Story."
我觉得更像《异想天开》  不过...
I was thinking more "Fantasticks," But...
关键是...
Look, the point is...
我们不会告诉任何人的
We ain't telling nobody nothing.
你们也不能  明白吗
And neither are you, capisce?
"明白吗"
"Capisce."
稍等一下
Can you give us a second?
行
Sure.
他说我们要按剧本走
Okay, look, he says we need to follow the script.
我们现在身处音乐剧里
We're in a musical.
所以如果我们能说服他们向父亲坦白
So I think if we convince them to tell their fathers that
说他们恋爱了  我们也许就能出去
they're in love, maybe that'll get us out of here.
然后回家做...
And back home to being...
做单身汉...
single, yay...
至少我们可以一起做单身汉
At least we'll be single together.
这样说会让我们谁舒服一点吗
Has saying that ever made anyone feel better?
可能吧
Debatable.
好吧  所以...
Okay, so look...
你们的父亲并不完美  对吧
Your fathers aren't perfect, right?
爱情也不是完美的
Love isn't perfect.
没错  但你不能因为爱着一个人
No, but you can't let your love for somebody
就害怕面对将要发生的事
cause you to be afraid of what might happen.
无论是好是坏  你都得接受
You gotta take the good with the bad, no matter what.
-没错  -那也包括...
- Right. - And that includes...
告诉你们的父亲  你们对彼此的感觉
telling your fathers how you two feel about each other.
好吧  你说得很有道理
All right, you make a convincing argument.
-真的  -我们会说的
- You do. - We'll do it.
我们会告诉他们的  对吗
We'll tell them about us, right?
-我们应该现在就去  -好的
- Well, we should go now. - Okay.
谢了  孩子
Gee, thanks, kid.
-给你  -谢谢
- For you. - Thank you.
好吧
Okay.
在音乐剧里说服别人...
Convincing people in musicals is...
-真是简单  -没错
- really easy. - Yeah.
希望从这里出去也能一样简单
Let's hope getting out of one is just as easy.
迪格西
Digsy!
她回来了
She's back!
谢天谢地你没事
Thank God you're safe.
我当然没事
Oh, of course I'm safe.
巴里和卡拉说  是你们派他们找我的
Barry and Kara told me that you sent them to find me.
我们很担心
We were concerned.
爸爸们  没什么好担心的
Dads, there's no reason to be concerned.
"爸爸们"
"Dads"?
你有意见吗
You got a problem with that?
没有
No.
我爱音乐剧  所以...
I love musicals, so...
好吧
Okay...
爸爸们  有件事...
Look, Dads, there's something that...
我要告诉你们
I need to tell you.
我恋爱了
I'm in love!
那个幸运男孩是谁
Who is the, uh-- the lucky boy?
托米·莫兰
Tommy Moran.
你说的是卡特·莫兰的儿子吗
You--you mean Cutter Moran's kid?
爸  听着  我们相爱了
Dad, look, we're in love.
你们相爱个鬼
The hell you are.
他是个流氓  他父亲也是个流氓
He's a hooligan! His father's a hooligan.
-他母亲  -打住
- His mother is-- - Hey!
别在小姑娘面前这么说
Not in front of the girl.
你不许爱那个男孩
And you're not loving that boy.
你脑子坏掉了吗
Have you lost your mind?
她是我夙敌的女儿
She is the daughter of my enemy.
迪格西·福斯就是个肮脏恶劣的无赖
Digsy Foss is a dirty, rotten scoundrel,
而那种父亲生下来的女儿也不会是什么好东西
and the apple doesn't fall far from the tree--
爸  你听我解释
Dad, if you just let me explain.
没什么好解释的  托米
There's nothing to explain, Tommy.
我知道你一直有事瞒着我
I knew you were keeping something from me.
但我从未想过居然是这种事
I never imagined it was something like this!
她已经不是你捧在手心里的那个小女孩了
She isn't your little girl anymore.
她不是了
Well, she isn't.
她已经是一位非常勇敢坚强的女性了
She's an incredibly brave, strong woman.
只要一眼  就能看得出来
One look, and you can see that.
而她想跟他在一起
And she wants to be with him.
不管她有多么害怕告诉你这件事
No matter how scared she was to tell you,
不管和他在一起会是多么危险
no matter how dangerous it is to be with him,
重要的是  他们在一起
all that matters is, they're together.
而当你找到那样的真爱
And when you find a love like that, well...
你就应该好好把握
you gotta hold on to it.
不管是谁试图阻止你
No matter who's trying to stop you.
这一点我现在反正是想明白了
That's clear to me now.
我觉得你对你儿子有点过于严厉了
I think you're being a little tough on your son.
什么
Excuse me?
很明显这就是为什么他不敢把事情当即就告诉你
Well, it's obvious why he didn't tell you right away.
我是说  看看你对此的反应
I mean, look at the way you're reacting.
或许你就先听听他的理由
Maybe if you just listen and-- and hear his reasons
尝试一下从他的角度来看待问题
and try to see things from his point of view...
或许  或许你就能理解这件事他为什么之前
maybe--maybe you'd understand why he didn't tell you...
不告诉你了
before now.
宝贝  只是
Baby doll, it's just--
你永远不会理解作为一位父亲意味着什么
you'll never understand what it means to be a father.
米莉  我的心肝宝贝  我们一直呵护着你
Millie, my darling, we've always taken care of you.
我们只是想让你开心
We just want you to be happy.
*天鹅绒  我多希望*
*Velvet, I can wish you*
*你的外套衣领丝滑柔软*
*For the collar of your coat*
*一路坦途  幸运常相伴*
*And fortune smiling all along your way*
*但我最希望*
*But more I cannot wish you*
*你能找到毕生所爱*
*Than to wish you find your love*
*拥有人生真爱*
*Your own true love this day*
*玉宇琼楼  我多希望*
*Mansions, I can wish you*
*七名仆人  红衣华服相随*
*Seven footmen, all in red*
*银盘盛着名片*
*And calling cards upon a silver tray*
*但我最希望*
*But more I cannot wish you*
*你能找到毕生所爱*
*Than to wish you find your love*
*拥有人生真爱*
*Your own true love this day*
*站在这里*
*Standing there*
*凝望着你*
*Gazing at you*
*目光深情暧昧*
*With the sheep's eye*
*露出甘甜微笑*
*And a licorice tooth*
*音乐响起  我多希望*
*Music I can wish you*
*美妙音乐伴你成长*
*Merry music while you're young*
*等到发丝花白*
*And wisdom when your hair*
*更有满腹才华*
*Has turned to gray*
*但我最希望*
*But more I cannot wish you*
*你能找到毕生所爱*
*Than to wish you find your love*
*拥有人生真爱*
*Your own true love this day*
*目光深情暧昧*
*With a sheep's eye*
*露出甘甜微笑*
*And a licorice tooth*
*还有强壮的臂膀*
*And the strong arms*
*陪伴你一生*
*To carry you away*
*一生*
*Away*
*还有强壮的臂膀*
*And the strong arms*
*陪伴你一生*
*To carry you away*
谢谢你跟我们说实话  宝贝
Thanks for telling us the truth, baby.
我太爱你们两位了
I love you both so much.
我们也爱你
We love you.
谢谢
Thanks.
好了
Okay...
那么接下来你准备怎么办
So what do you want to do?
把小伙子们都召集起来
Gather up the boys.
-我们要开战了  -我也这么觉着
- We're going to war. - I had a feeling.
我很欣赏你的诚实  儿子
I appreciate your honesty, son.
谢谢  老爸
Thanks, Dad.
过来
Come here.
把小伙子们都召集起来
Get the boys.
我们要开战了
We are going to war.
瞧瞧谁来了
Well, well, well...
这不是我
If it isn't the two people
最想见的那两位吗
I was hoping would visit me the most.
立刻把他们恢复原状
Fix them. Now.
抱歉  我做不到
I'm sorry. I can't.
如果你还想走出这间牢房的话
If you ever want to get out of that cell,
那就给我老老实实去做
that's exactly what you're gonna do.
你不懂
You don't get it.
你不明白  大块头
You don't understand, big guy.
这样是不行的
That's just not how it works.
我的超能力不是那样运作的
My powers don't work that way.
你在说什么  是你把他们搞成那样的
What do you mean? You're the one who did this to them.
是的  但
Yes, but...
现在只有他们
they are the only ones that are in control
能控制自己的情况
of what happens to them now,
还有你俩
as are the two of you.
我们吗  你在说什么
Us? What does that mean?
你爱他...
How much...
有多深  爱瑞丝
do you love him, Iris?
还有你  蒙·艾尔  你爱她有多深
And you, Mon-El, how much do you love her?
所以问题是
So the question is:
有强大到能够救他们吗
is that strong enough to save them?
你们要卡拉和巴里回到原来的世界
You want Kara and Barry back from the world they're in,
你们自己去把他们带出来
you can go get them yourselves.
你们有这种力量
You have that power.
怎么做
How?
我不能告诉你们
Ah, I can't tell you.
抱歉  你们得自己搞明白
Sorry, you gotta figure it out yourself.
现在  如果你们不介意  我要在
Now, if you don't mind, I'm gonna just chill
你们这装饰得挺棒的小牢房放松一下
in this wonderfully decorated little cell of yours.
再见  各位
Bye, guys!
祝好运  爱会找到解决方法
Good luck. Love will find a way.
你们能做到
You can do it.
爱的力量之类的
Power of love and all that.
现在我们怎么做
What do we do now?
我们让米莉和托米
We got-- we got Millie and Tommy
告诉他们的父亲他们相爱了
to tell their fathers that they're in love.
虽然我知道这一切都是音乐剧
Which, I know we're in a musical and everything,
但看到蒙·艾尔跟别人相爱...
but seeing Mon-El in love with someone else was--
让人很难接受  我知道
It was hard to watch. I know.
不过  我们...
Anyway, I mean, what are we...
该怎么做呢  你认为音乐大师
supposed to do? What do you think this...
现在要我们怎么做
Music Meister needs us to do now?
原来你们在这里
Ah, there you are!
你俩准备好了吗
You two ready?
准备好什么
Ready for...
准备好排演  笨蛋
For rehearsal, you dolt.
莫兰先生告诉我你还保留了
Mr. Moran told me that you got more songs
很多歌曲
in your repertoire.
我们要完成音乐剧
We have to finish the musical.
-是的  -你知道...
- Yeah. - Uh, do you...
你刚好会创作吧
do you happen to know anything original?
事实上
As a matter of fact,
我一整天都在努力创作
I've been working on something all day.
-在音乐剧里事情真的比较简单  -是的
- Things really are easier in musicals. - Yeah.
好吧
All right.
*此时此刻*
*At times like these*
*生活不如我意*
*When life is getting me down*
*世界似乎濒临终结*
*And the world seems like it's gonna end-ship*
*你我之间*
*There's at least one power*
*至少还有一种力量*
*That we both still have*
*那就是*
*And that's the power of...*
*友谊的力量*
*Friendship*
对  我本来要这么唱的
Yeah, that's exactly what I was gonna say.
这个很好押韵
Yeah, it's an easy rhyme.
*我是你的超级朋友*
*I'm your super friend*
*你的超级朋友*
*Your super friend*
*紧要关头我会挺身而出*
*I'll be there in the nick of time*
*但凡你有任何危险*
*If you're ever in a spot*
*如果你不能及时赶到*
*And if you're not there in time*
*那就回到过去  再来一次*
*You can just go back in time and give it another shot*
我本来不打算再那么做的
I'm actually not supposed to do that anymore.
好吧
Oh, okay.
唱
Sing!
*我是你的超级朋友*
*I'm your super friend*
*超级朋友*
*Super friend*
*每当你需要赞美*
*When you need a compliment*
*我能飞快说出一堆赞美*
*I can rattle off a dozen*
*比如  我得说我一点也不佩服*
*For instance, I have to say, I'm not impressed..*
*你那更出名的堂弟*
*By your more famous cousin*
谢谢你  没人那么说过
Thank you! No one ever says that.
他像是这么说"我是超人"
Oh, he's all, like, "I'm Superman."
-真是让人印象深刻  -谢谢
- That's a really good impression. - Thanks.
*我是你的超级朋友*
*I'm your super friend*
*超级朋友*
*Super friend*
*要说起好友  朋友  你就是最佳*
*When it comes to buddies, pal, you're the best*
*比起我胸前的闪电球*
*I love you more than the lightning bolt*
*我更中意于你*
*I wear on my chest*
*你要是伤心难过*
*If you're ever sad...*
*我会送上鲜花*
*I'll bring you flowers*
*女高音也是你的超能力之一*
*And you can list soprano as one of your powers*
-*你要是身无分文*  -*我有大把钞票*
- *If you're ever broke * - *I've got the cash*
-*我家的沙发*  -*欢迎过来凑合*
- *On my couch * - *You're welcome to crash*
*你要是需要帮忙*
*And if you ever need a hand*
*我定会如闪电般飞奔而来*
*I'll be there in a flash*
-巴里  -真有意思
- Barry! - That was funny.
*我是你的超级*
*I'm your super...*
*这可是一语双关*
*That has a double meaning*
*朋友*
*Friend*
你好  我的朋友
Hello, my friend.
我们的女儿嫁给
It will be a cold day in hell
你们任何一个人的儿子是永不到来之时
before our daughter marries any son of yours.
就像他说的
Like he said.
永不到来之时
A cold, cold day.
你说了我正要说的话
You took the words right out of my mouth.
快走
Come on.
住手
Stop!
巴里
Barry!
天啊
Oh, my God.
-怎么了  -我们快失去他们了
- What's wrong? - I think we're losing them.
你能阻止吗
Can you stop it?
不知道原因就阻止不了
Not if I don't know why.
我们要怎么做
What are we gonna do?
不管他们在哪个世界我们都要过去
We need to go to whatever world they're in.
我们要怎么过去
How are we gonna do that?
他说  如果我们对他们的爱够深
Look, he said, if we loved them enough
不管他们在哪里我们都能救他们
that we could save them, wherever they are.
西斯科  你可以用震波带我们过去
Cisco, you can vibe us there.
我认为这行不通
I don't think it works that way.
你曾把我送去神速力
You sent me into the Speed Force.
你曾把巴里和沃利送去未来
You sent Barry and Wally into the future.
这难不倒你
You can do this too.
她在说什么
What is she talking about?
-什么是震波  -我迟点再解释
- What's a vibe? - I'll explain later.
来吧  抓着我的肩膀
Come on, just... grab on to my shoulders.
希望这样能行
Let's hope this works.
巴里  巴里
Barry, Barry...
卡拉
Kara...
巴里
Barry!
卡拉
Kara!
-不  -不
- Oh, no. - No.
是我
Hey, it's me.
是爱瑞丝  我来了
It's Iris, I'm here. Hi.
别离开我  我会带你出去的
Stay with me. I'm gonna get you out.
没时间了
There's no time.
我们得走了
We have to go.
我们得带他们出去
We have to get them out!
加油  巴里  巴里
Come on, Barry. Barry!
不
No!
我很抱歉我对你说谎了
I'm so sorry I lied to you.
我原谅你
I forgive you.
我爱你
I love you.
不  巴里  巴里  你会没事的
No, Barry, Barry, you're gonna be okay.
我爱你
I love you.
爱瑞丝
Iris?
蒙·艾尔
Mon-El?
他们回来了
They're back!
好极了  热烈鼓掌
Bravo! Round of applause!
起立鼓掌  太棒了
Standing O. It was so good!
我很喜欢  很精彩的演出
I loved it. That was a hell of a show.
而你俩...
And you two...
你们的爱果然足够强大
I guess your love really was strong enough after all.
漂亮
Beautiful.
老兄  你怎么逃出那个牢房的
Man, how did you get out of the cell?
西斯科  你真的认为那个牢房
Cisco, do you really think that cell
能关得住我吗
is gonna just, like, hold me?
不  我很抱歉  到底怎么回事
No, I'm sorry-- what's going on?
你为什么这么对我们
Why did you do this to us?
我这么做是因为我相信好人
I did it because I believe in the good guys.
我们初次见面时我跟你说过了
I told you when we first met.
是要给你们所有人上一堂课
It was to teach all of you a lesson.
因为我看见一切
'Cause I see everything,
我看见两个人
and I saw two people...
两颗破碎的心
with two broken hearts.
所以这堂课是...
So the lesson was...
爱  超女
Love, Supergirl.
爱就要...
Love is about...
让自己被救
letting yourself be saved.
不只是要拯救其他人
It's not just about saving other people.
就算你们是超级英雄
Even if you are superheroes.
总之  我很抱歉我
Anyway, I'm sorry that I had to, like,
给你们捣了一点乱
mess with you a little bit.
我只是试着让你加入游戏
I was just trying to get you to play the game,
唱歌和跳舞
do the song and dance.
你是来自
Are you, like, from another--
多元宇宙的其他地球之类的吗
Earth-multi-verse-- universe, something?
是的...
Yeah, you...
你甚至无法明白我来自哪里
you wouldn't even understand where I come from.
等一下  抱歉  就那样吗
Wait, I'm sorry, that's it?
你又要去给别人上课了吗
You're just gonna teach somebody else a lesson?
是的  我正打算那么做
Yeah, that's exactly what I'm gonna do.
*想起你的同胞时*
*Think of your fellow man*
*援助之手别吝惜*
*Lend him a helping hand*
*放一份爱在心里*
*Put a little love in your heart*
等一下  我来理清楚
Wait, so, let me get this straight.
你被人下咒了  他叫...
You got whammied by some guy named...
音乐大师
Music Meister.
该死  巴里  我会花一大笔钱
Damn, Barry, I'd have paid good money
来看你的歌舞
to see you singing and dancing.
可别了
No.
巴里一直瞒着你们
Well, he's holding out on you
其实他有天籁之音
because Barry has an amazing voice.
没错
He does!
我其实看过他唱歌
I've actually seen him sing.
什么  真的吗
What? You have?
我们怎么没把那个做成动态图片
How have we not made a GIF of that?
好吧  严格来说  我不是这里唯一
Well, technically, I'm not even the only one here
会唱歌的人
who can sing.
-谢谢你  BA  -什么
- Thank you, B.A. - What?
我说的是卡拉
I was talking about Kara.
等一下  你也是吗
Wait, shh--oh, you too?
卡拉  卡拉当然会唱歌
Kara. Of course Kara can sing.
好吧  她叫超女
Well, her name is Supergirl.
这隐含了什么吧
It's kind of implied, right?
好吧  我们得走了
Well, we better be getting going.
我答应卡拉的姐姐  我们会带完好的她回去
I promised Kara's sister we'd get her back in one piece.
没有你我们做不到
We couldn't have done this without you.
-谢谢  -谢谢
- Thank you. - Thank you.
你们怎么样
How are you guys doing?
我们会没事的
Yeah, I think we'll be okay.
如果你再对我说谎
Although, if you lie to me again,
我会把一座山压在你身上
I will drop a mountain on you.
你这是比喻吗
You mean figuratively?
不  是地质学上
No, I mean, geologically.
好吧
Okay.
那你们呢
What about you guys?
再看吧
We'll see.
我搬去跟西斯科住时你完全没动过这里
You didn't change anything when I moved in with Cisco.
我无法这么做
I, um, couldn't bring myself to do it.
过去三年  我们经历了很多事
You know, we've been through a lot these last three years,
但...
but, um...
被困在音乐剧里
getting stuck in a musical?
音乐大师
Music Meister
说我可以做任何事
said that, you know, I could've been anything,
但我创造那个世界是因为
that I created that world because...
你在看着他们
You were watching them.
因为我们
Because of us.
我妈以前总是说音乐剧有
My mom used to always say that musicals have the power
让一切变得更好的力量
to make everything better.
成功了吗
Did it work?
回家与你相依相靠
*无法预见未来的走向*
*Can't say how the days will unfold*
*无法改变未来的去向*
*Can't change what the future may hold*
*但我希望未来有你*
*But I want you in it*
*时时刻刻  每分每秒*
*Every hour, every minute*
*世界或许瞬息万变*
*This world can race by far too fast*
*一切都在流逝  很难预见*
*Hard to see while it's all flying past*
*但此刻清楚明了*
*But it's clear now*
*此刻你就在我面前*
*When you're standing here now*
*我真心诚意*
*I am meant to be*
*不论你在我身边何处*
*Wherever you are next to me*
*我只想要*
*All I want to do*
*回家与你相依相靠*
*Is come runnin' home to you*
*Come runnin' home to you*
*我保证毕生都将*
*And all my life, I promise to*
*奔回家里  与你相依相靠*
*Keep runnin' home to you*
*我能预见*
*And I could see it*
*从一开始  从最开始*
*Right from the start, right from the start*
*就认定你是*
*That you would be*
*黑暗中我的明灯  黑暗中的明灯*
*Be my light in the dark, light in the dark*
*你让我别无选择*
*Oh, you gave me no other choice*
*只能爱恋你*
*But to love you*
*我只想要*
*All I want to do*
*回家与你相依相靠*
*Is come runnin' home to you*
*Come runnin' home to you*
*我保证毕生都将*
*And all my life I promise to*
*奔回家里  与你相依相靠*
*Keep runnin' home to you*
*奔回家里*
*Keep runnin' home*
*与你相依相靠*
*Home to you*
*无法预见未来的走向*
*Can't say how the days will unfold*
*无法改变未来的去处*
*Can't change what the future may hold*
*但我想未来有你*
*But I want you in it*
*时时刻刻  每分每秒*
*Every hour, every minute*
爱瑞丝·韦斯特
Iris West,
你愿意嫁给我吗
will you marry me?
我愿意
Yes.